John V. Dowdy, Sr. papers, Inclusive: 1926-1986, undated; Bulk: 1952-1972, undated.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Trial and Imprisonment, 1950-1978, undated; 8
  - Statement, McMillan, John L., 1970 June (Box 509, Folder 8)
  - Statement, Poage, W.R., House of Representatives, 1972 October 14 (Box 509, Folder 9)
  - Statement, Teague, Olin E., 1970 May 12 (Box 509, Folder 10)
  - Tapes, Cassette, E-3859NQ, 1976 July 20 (Box 509, Folder 11)
  - Tapes, Cassette, Clark with Dowdy, 1976 April 26 (Box 509, Folder 12)
  - Tapes, Cassette, Dowdy-Clark, undated (Box 509, Folder 13)
  - Tapes, Reel-to-Reel, KTLU, circa 1974 (Box 509, Folder 14)
  - Tapes, Reel-to-Reel, Monarch Construction Co. Investigation by D.C. Committee, undated (Box 509, Folder 15)
  - Tapes, Reel-to-Reel, Q9 E-3752 & E-3859 NQ, 1976 May 27 (Box 509, Folder 16)
  - Tapes, Reel-to-Reel, Nathan Cohen & Dowdy (digital copy available), 1970 January 20 (Box 510, Folder 1)
  - Tapes, Reel-to-Reel, [Poyrnich], undated (Box 510, Folder 2)
  - Tapes, Reel-to-Reel, Press Conference re: Charles Wilson’s False Sworn Statement in JD’s Campaign, undated (Box 510, Folder 3)
  - Tapes, Reel-to-Reel, Telephone, 1973 January 7 (Box 510, Folder 4)
  - Tapes Transcripts, Cohen & Dowdy, circa 1970’s (Box 510, Folder 5)
  - Tapes Transcripts, Conversation between SP Haines & Gerald M. Thompson, 1972 January 3 (Box 510, Folder 6)
  - Telephone, List of Calls, 1965 (Box 510, Folder 7)
  - Telephone, List of Calls, 1969 (Box 510, Folder 8)
  - Telephone, List of Calls, 1970 (Box 510, Folder 9)
  - Telephone Transcripts, Nathan Cohen & Dowdy, 1970 January 13 (Box 510, Folder 10)
  - Telephone Transcripts, Nathan Cohen & Dowdy, 1970 January 19 (Box 510, Folder 11)
  - Telephone Transcripts, Nathan Cohen & Dowdy, 1970 January 20 (Box 510, Folder 12)
  - Telephone Transcripts, Nathan Cohen & Dowdy, 1970 January 28 (Box 510, Folder 13)
  - Telephone Transcripts, Myrvin Clark & Dowdy, circa 1974 (Box 510, Folder 14)
  - Telephone Transcripts, Myrvin Clark & Dowdy, 1974 November (Box 510, Folder 15)
  - Travel, 1965-1969 (Box 510, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts, Opening Statements, 1971 November 9 (Box 511, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, Government, Cohen Testimony (1 of 2), 1971 November 10 (Box 511, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, Government, Cohen Testimony (2 of 2), 1971 November 10 (Box 511, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, Government, Cohen Testimony (1 of 2), 1971 November 11 (Box 511, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, Government, Cohen Testimony (2 of 2), 1971 November 11 (Box 511, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, Government, Cohen Testimony (1 of 2), 1971 November 15 (Box 511, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, Government, Cohen Testimony (2 of 2), 1971 November 15 (Box 511, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, Government, Meyer, John Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 511, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, Government, Leroy C. Lerch, 1971 November 16 (Box 551, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, Government, Clarence J. Kochendorfer Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 511, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, Government, Julius Levitt Testimony (1 of 2), 1971 November 16 (Box 511, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, Government, Julius Levitt Testimony (2 of 2), 1971 November 16 (Box 512, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, Government, Floyd Celey Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 512, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, Government, Thelma Cohen Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 512, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, Government, Stanley Silver Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 512, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, Government, Ralph Clark Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 512, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, Government, Daniel Pope Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 512, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, Government, Charlotte K. Reynolds Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 512, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, Government, Elmer L. Tarwater, Jr. Testimony, 1971 November 16 (Box 512, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, Government, Vernice Parrott Testimony, 1971 November 22 (Box 512, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, Government, Myrvin C. Clark Testimony, 1971 November 22 (Box 512, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, Government, Myrvin C. Clark Testimony, 1971 November 23 (Box 512, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, Government, Harry A. Finney Testimony, 1971 November 24 (Box 512, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, Government, James B. Hobbs Testimony, 1971 November 24 (Box 512, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, Government, Garland Bell, 1971 November 29 (Box 512, Folder 14)
  - Transcripts, Government, Discussion of Tape Quality and Use of Sound Experts, 1971 November 29 (Box 513, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, Government, Alfred Hantman Testimony, 1971 November 29 (Box 513, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, Government, William Paul Green Testimony, 1971 November 29 (Box 513, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, Government, Layne Bonner Testimony, 1971 November 29 (Box 513, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, Government, Marion M. Wright Testimony, 1971 November 29 (Box 513, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, Government, Marion M. Wright and Layne Bonner Testimony, 1971 November 30 (Box 513, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, Government, Arguments for Jury using Transcript of meeting between Dowdy & Cohen, 1971 November 30 (Box 513, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Oliver Dibble Testimony, 1971 November 30 (Box 513, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Michael Eisenmenger Testimony, 1971 December 1 (Box 513, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Hayden S. Garber Testimony, 1971 December 1 (Box 513, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Hayden S. Garber Testimony, 1971 December 2 (Box 513, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Leonard Wilson Testimony, 1971 December 2 (Box 513, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Leonard Wilson Testimony (1 of 2), 1971 December 6 (Box 513, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Leonard Wilson Testimony (2 of 2), 1971 December 6 (Box 513, Folder 14)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Leonard Wilson Testimony, 1971 December 7 (Box 514, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, Defense, John V. Dowdy Testimony, 1971 December 13 (Box 514, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, Defense, John V. Dowdy Testimony (1 of 2), 1971 December 14 (Box 514, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, Defense, John V. Dowdy Testimony (2 of 2), 1971 December 14 (Box 514, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, Defense, John V. Dowdy Testimony, 1971 December 15 (Box 514, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, Defense, John V. Dowdy Testimony, 1971 December 16 (Box 514, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Earle Cabell, Olin Teague and W. R. Poage Testimonies, 1971 December 15 (Box 514, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Kenneth Gray, Andrew Jacobs Jr., W. Pat Jennings Testimonies, 1971 December 15 (Box 514, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Alice Paul, Raul G. Salinas, John Mason, Ronald Haas Testimonies, 1971 December 15 (Box 514, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Charles A. Morgan, Duane L. Koch Testimonies, 1971 December 16 (Box 515, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Character Witnesses, 1971 December 16 (Box 515, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Raymond Deison, Jr., John Morse, Jesse Summers Testimonies, 1971 December 17 (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Don Johnson Testimony, 1971 December 17 (Box 515, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Mrs. Clifton Parrott, Grayson Foster Testimonies, 1971 December 20 (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Gerald Yoes, Verna Collins, Maxine Dean Testimonies, 1971 December 20 (Box 515, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Garland V. Bell, John V. Dowdy, Jr., William Thompson, Jr. Testimonies, 1971 December 21 (Box 515, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, Defense, Jennie Hankins, Julian Paul Green, James A. Park, Robert J. Stevens, Harold M. Widener Testimonies, 1971 December 21 (Box 515, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, Government, Exhibits Read into Transcript, 1971 December 21 (Box 516, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, Government, Lyndel Shaneyfelt, Verna M. Collins Testimonies, 1971 December 22 (Box 516, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, Government, Elmer L. Tarwater, Myron Miller, Alfred R. Berry, Nathan Cohen and Others’ Testimonies, 1971 December 22 (Box 516, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, Government, John Dowdy and others; Offering Exhibits in to Evidence, 1971 December 22 (Box 516, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, Appendix, circa 1972 (Box 516, Folder 5)